Hello everyone, this is NiyariColejoy, and today's project is the first S-Beauty.
Today's project is to see who knows the most about Lennon.
NiyaJoi is new to this, so we're going to start with the king of NiyaJoi, Lennon, who has been the center of NiyaJoi for many times. I'm sorry, but...
I'm sorry, but I don't think I can say anymore.
I love him and we've had dinner together.
I think I've been trying to get all the answers right.
How about you?
I'm confident about the riddle.
I think I can do it.
Confident?
Not at all.
No?
Because it's hard.
Of course it's hard.
I'm really like everyone else at home.
It's really easy.
So let's get right to it.
Question 1: What was your dream when you were a child?
Well, that's a tough one.
This one's easy.
You've never said it?
I've never said it.
Most kids would write it like this.
What?
Most girls...
I'm writing a lot of boyish stuff now.
I used to like cute things.
You know, like, my mom used to make all my clothes and stuff.
She decided all my clothes and stuff.
She used to make me wear half-twins and stuff like that.
I had a haircut like Frasier's here.
It's a classic.
I'm sure you can tell by the way she did it.
How's it look? Did you like it?
It went well.
Let's see what everyone else's answers are.Then let's see everyone's answers.
Seino
Open!
Yes, that's right!
Cake shop
Flower shop
Cake shop!
Oh!
I'll give you these two when I get to the regulars.
That's right.
I thought about being a cartoonist, but...
But you said you were a cartoonist when you were little.
Let's watch the VCR for the correct answer.
Okay, okay.
Wait.
It's like Lennon talks.
Legendary.
What?
Oh, I'm a pastry chef.
You're close.
Alice, close.
This is OK.
Is this the patissier of the cake shop?
A patissier of a cake shop?
It's a cake baker.
A cake baker.
Like tempering.
Yes, yes, yes.
You want to do some tempering.
Well, well, well, well, I'll take Lennon's kindness over this one.
I'm the opposite of king.
Thank you very much.
I'm the king.
A king, indeed.Wang, indeed, is king.
I lost.
Wait a minute.
What?
The florist's shop is like lunch.
What? No way.
What's your shop called?
It's not right?
No, it's not.
That's not it!
Boo-boo!
There's too many of them.
It's true.
What's wrong with you?
The first question...
These two.
Julie and Ayumi get 1 point.
One point.
Now the next question
What did you enjoy the most in your first year of Nearly Call 10th?
What was the most fun?
Think about the first year.
How far into your first year?
So, until March.
Until March, I guess.
You're not going in, are you?
I'm not going in.
That's not going in.
That was the best part. That was really fun.
It was fun.
Shooting music videos.
Ayumi's good at making decisions.
I think she was laughing at one point.I think she laughed in an instant.
Time with Julie.
Oh, hey.
Don't look at me like that.
What are you looking at?
It wasn't all fun and games.
I mean, it wasn't all fun, but it was fun all the same.
Wait, wait, wait, I don't understand.
I don't know, there's two of them.
Did you write two? Can I write two?
No... no... no... no...
Ayumi.
Let's see your answers.
Open!
Okay.
What? You wrote that the first time.
I wrote that?
The special performance.
But I wrote it for a second.
I wrote it for a second and then thought about it.
Ayumi... you wrote this first.
I like Lion a lot.
I love lions.
Like the world of lions.
Yes.
The costumes...
What if it's a lion?
The correct VCR?
Yes, please.
Is this your second year on stage?
I thought you were on stage.
First year, second year, no.
Then it's a special performance.
Yay!
So far, so good... but I can still go... because I did that special voice, too.
I'm going to do Lion, because it's the most fun to be a lion in a live performance.Lions are the most fun at a live performance, after all.
The special performance, I was so excited, I could remember every song.
It was kind of hard, but I don't know...
I'm not having fun?
I don't know what it's like to be in Philando.
We spent a lot of time together, and there were so many of us... and we played together every day.
That's why I feel like we got to know each other better.
With each event, the distance between us is getting closer, isn't it?
It's true, I wonder what's going to happen in a few years...
We're family now.
I get one point for that.
Ai, aren't you strong?
You're kidding, right?
Next question.
What's the best part about Esbirellon?
This is really easy.
You're good.
Wait a minute... you're really good... at something you just said.
No comment.
No comments.
Appearance?
I'm not talking to myself.
It's not about the eyes.
No, no, no, no, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm sure you'll all remember me.
Did you open it? Did you guys open it?
Did you open it? Ready?
Doo!
Eyes.
Oh!
Shortness of breath.
I'm out.
Ayamen, you're making me short of breath right now.
I'm pushing on Ayamen's hand.
Kinik.The kinik.
This uuuh
It's so great.
It comes out the best.
Ayamen's eyes looking at Lennon with a heart
When the members take pictures of Lennon and ask each other
or ask each other about Lennon's picture or something
she asked if she could have the pictures.
We airdropped all of them.
When Lennon danced on social media
There was a guy who made me gasp.
I love that sentence.
It's got kinik.
Ahh...
I don't know... dancing...
Melo's dance is so crisp and clear.
If you follow that, it's Kinik.
She's talking about having a Lennon vibe.
That's what I was thinking.
That's what I thought.
Okay, let's see if we got it right.
This way.
What?
Your hair keeps changing.
Oh, my God!
I don't know. He said "Wolf".
No, but, you know, it changes all the time.
It changes a lot.
Yes, it changes.
He's changing so much, isn't he?
He's changing a lot.
It's fun to watch, isn't it?
It's always changing.
We were all right this time.
Shoo!
It's all in the looks.It's all about appearances, right?
Here's the next question.
We're down to Esme Lennon's best face.
Three, two, one.
Do you mean the kind of face I'm going to make?
Do you mean you'll do it?
Three, two, one.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Didn't you see it?
We both just made some kind of hand gesture.
Oh, I did it.
Oh, hey, Etta.
I'm just gonna take a look at this.
I'm gonna get you a keeper, and I'm gonna get you into a good position.
You're right.
I'll give you a standing insertion that'll look good on you.
This could be it.
Pose, pose. They don't pose all the time.
They're getting beat up.
That's for sure.
Okay, here's the correct answer.
Three, two, one.
Wow!
You're right.
That's for sure.
Are you sure about that? Are you sure about this?
Yeah, I've got it.
I always see it at the regular show.
Usually live.
The look on Lennon's face.
Smile.
Surely you're right.
No, min-chan.
It's the only facial pattern I can find.
Eh, Min-chanEh, Min-chan
this one or this one
This one or this one.
This is the only one I'll do.
This is so frustrating
It's so frustrating
Come on, Melita.
Next question.
This way.
Describe how you feel right now.
What if I can't draw?
You see this picture here?
It looks like Totoro.
Wait a minute.
I'm not very good at drawing what I want to draw.
What should I do if I can't express what I have in my mind?
Lennon was a good drawer.
He was good.
Lennon is a good drawer.
Let's start with Jerry.
Ready?
Go on, go on, go on.
You'll get your message across.
These... these dots, what are they?
They mean you're hungry.
Drool.
Too much?
Too much drool?
It's kind of pink.
His eyes are kind of slanted.
It's like his eyes are darting in different directions.
Okay, then, Aimee, please.
There you go.
What's that?
Same.
You look refreshed.It's refreshing.
Not at all.
Is it similar?
A little bit.
What's that look?
I don't know.
He's in a good mood.
I'm in a good mood.
I'll go.
Okay, everybody.
Cats!
Wait a minute.
You look hungry.
You said you were hungry earlier.
I thought maybe it was a food thing.
Then please show us the correct answer.
I'm good at drawing.
I don't know how to say it.
I don't know what to say. I'm in a big hurry.
You're in a hurry?
Yes, I'm in a hurry.
Wait, you're in a hurry?
Are you in a hurry?
By the way, this is Chiba.
That's right.
It's Rin-chan, right?
Call her a cat.
I didn't say that.
I didn't say cat.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Shouldn't we risk it?Maybe we should risk it.
Let's give up now.
Here's how it went.
Julie has 1 point.
Aimee has 0 points.
Aimee has 2 points.
Three more questions to go.
I can still do it. I can still do it.
These 3 questions are so easy!
Very easy.
Here are the questions.
What was your first impression of Julie Aoumeda?
This one is really easy.
This is the truth.
First meeting, right?
You know how sometimes people say they have a different impression of you when they meet you for the first time?
No, it's the same.
It's the same.
That's a great clue.
What?
Open all your answers at once!
Okay.
How are you?
She's very energetic.
Shut up.
But now that I think about it, we've never met.
I see.
I think I get it.
I'm gonna keep talking to her.
I don't think I'd be very comfortable talking to you if I didn't know you.
I mean, we were playing video games.
That's great.
He's talking a lot.
He talked a lot.He talked so much.
Every year.
He talked so much, I remember.
Here's the correct answer.
He really is just so bright!
I really thought he was a little charm ghost.
It's everyone's fault
I mean...
I know.
I was going to write cheerful.
Cheerful and cheerful are the same thing, aren't they?
I thought "noisy" was a little too charming.
How's that?
What?
Harsh.
He's harsh.
He's loud and cheerful.
Anyway, I'm gonna give you two the green light.
Yay!
You sure about that?
Yes!
Oh, no.
This is where it starts to get ugly.
We've got to start targeting the right answers.
Here's the next problem.
With Ayumi Ichihara...
A date with Ayumi Ichihara during summer vacation.
Where did you two go?
What?
I think we like each other.
What's this?
We talked about it once.
You did?
It's not coming.
This one's good, this one's good.
Overseas?Overseas?
Oh, my God.
It's about time.
Domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic domestic
Domestic, domestic, domestic.
I'm sure it's domestic.
Distant?
Hey...
Ayumi...
I think she's good.
Mental?
Brainwashing?
Brainwashing.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go.
Jan.
Seth.
Summer festival
Your favorite artist or something like that.
Some of them say...
Or genres...
I don't know.
They're all saying it.
I want to go to Yuri's, too.
She says it all the time.
She's from Osaka.
Yuri's nice.
She's saying it! She's saying it!
He's saying it a lot!
He's saying it a lot.
But it's not a date.
Rock, it's not a date, right?Rocking's not a date, is it?
Yeah?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You want to hold hands and say "ehh"?
I'll do it. I'll do it.
I'm in. I'm in.
Let's watch the VTR.
Ayumi and I...
What?
It's summer vacation, right?
Let's see...
Music festival
Wow!
How loud!
With a voice?
In your voice?
That's amazing.
I thought it was amazing the moment he said it.
It was him.
It's him.
The other person...
We're not communicating.
Yes, I like music
Music
Because we have similar tastes
I'm sure
I knew him.
Male
Music.
But I also hear you talking about Univa.
I hear it a lot.
That's true.
I've seen idols who thought it was a good idea
Now for the next question.Now the next question
This way.
What?
It's just a big cow.
I don't want a big cow like this.
What kind of bull?
Hell.
What kind of...
Hell
What kind of hell is this?
You know, Elmo, I've been thinking about this a lot.
I don't want a big cow like this.
You're right.
I don't care what kind of bull it is.
It's okay.
Ai knew about this.
It's funny.
You have no idea.
No, it's funny.
It's funny.
What?
But Ayumi laughs at me just looking at me.
Everything's funny.
Did you go?
Yes, I did.
Now let's open the floor to everyone's answers.
Ta-da!
A cow...
It's funny!
Interesting
I'm amused.
Oroi oroi oroi oroi
Lovable
amusingamusing
Ai suddenly eats tea
Suddenly, Ai starts to push out a wrap
Suddenly he becomes a monk
Ai-chan
I have a strong image of Bob.
Ai-chan is always smiling, right?
If Ai suddenly shaved his head...
Like, "Good morning.
Good morning.
It's funny.
Good work today.
Good morning
push out
Ai.
You're right.
Looks good, but
But I'm afraid
It would be scary if you suddenly serve it during a lesson or something.
That's true.
What about you, Ai?
I'm going to go have some tea.
Bob out of nowhere.
Bob.
Bob. Bob.
bob
Bob
Ai...
I'm gonna go have some tea.
What?
Is that what's happening?
Like, wow.
I'm gonna go have some tea.
All the time.always
Always.
This way.
Yeah.
I don't want this tea.
I don't like it.
He speaks in a very fluent Osaka dialect.
It suits some people and not others.
You're right.
I see.
That's for sure.
This is not an essay to joke around with.
It's a serious one.
When you come in with something...
Good morning.
And then...
Ai, if you're all cozy...
It'll be fun if Ai's all cozy.
So, June is finished?
June's problem is over.
So, let's see the results!
Julie got 2 points!
Ayumi scored 1 point!
Ayumi got 4 points!
So, the 1st S-Meo is
Ayumi Ozawa!
Wow! That's amazing!
It's frustrating to hear myself say that!
It's hard because it's so whimsical!
I'm pretty free!
I'm just a cat!
I'm just saying whatever comes into my head!
From now on, I'll be proud.From now on, we will be magnificent.
I am S Meo! I'll be proud to say that I'm S-Meo!
Thank you very much!
You are awesome! Ayumi! You said so much that you weren't confident!
We were so screwed up,
We were so confident!
We were going to win!
So, that was S-Meo!
Bye bye!